Antonio Gonzalez

Cell: (206) 683-6781 | Email: goantonio31@outlook.com | Kirkland WA, 98034 LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/antonio-gonzalez-34a0771b0/ | Github: github.com/goantonioUW
Portfolio: goantoniouw.github.io/Portfolio/

Summary

Graduate of The University of Washington Full-Stack Web Development Bootcamp. Dynamic communicator who consistently exceeds goals and company expectations. Broad industry experience includes customer service, setting sales goals, and event coordination.

Projects

News Flow | Live link: news-flow | Github Repo: github.com/CoryKDev/news-flow | Interactive news application that gives users news based on the location they select.

- Role
 - o I focused on the front-end styling and creating a responsive UI.
- Technologies Used
 - o (MongoDB, Express, JWT, React, Bootstrap, Figma)

Name A Burger | Live link: name-a-burger.herokuapp.com | Github Repo: aithub.com/goantonioUW/burger
This application allows users to create a burger, move it to different tables and finally destroy the burger when finished.

- Role
- Creator of this complete project.
- Technologies used
 - o (MySQL, HandlebarsJs, NodeJS, Bootstrap, CSS)

Experience

Assistant Manager for Designer Shoes, Nordstrom, Bellevue, WA

2018-2021

- Trained and mentored new employees to achieve daily performance objectives.
- Greeted and assisted all customers daily in high-traffic retailer.
- Coached new team members on job tasks, performance strategies, and how to cross-sell.
- Boosted sales volume by coordinating and setting up events for major retailers
- Communicated and coordinated with multiple departments to achieve top results.

Account Manager, Wyndham Destinations, Redmond, WA

2018-2019

- Conducted one-on-one sales presentations and resort property tours to interested parties.
- Generated sales by prospecting leads, cold calling and negotiating advantageous deals.
- Identified customer needs to deliver relevant product solutions and promotions that met target budgets.
- Supported owner requests with pricing, property descriptions, room locations and portfolio information
- Attended professional training classes and assessments for continuous improvement.

Education

Full-Stack Web Development Bootcamp

2020-2021

University of Washington, Seattle, WA

Bellevue college 2013-2016

Associate of Arts: General Studies